Privacy Policy                    

===================================================================================================

|     |     |
| --- | --- | 
|     |     |

[TOP](https://www.childresearch.net/) > Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Child Research Net (CRN) is operated with the support of BERD (Benesse Educational Research and Development Institute). CRN observes [Benesse's Privacy Policy](https://www.benesse-hd.co.jp/en/utility/privacy.html) regarding all personal information provided or made available by visitors to this website.

|     |     |
| --- | --- | 
|     |     |

Latest Posts

* [\[Snuggling Up to Our Differences\] Episode 6: Sitting in a Chair and Listening--Good Manners?](https://www.childresearch.net/projects/special/2023_15.html)
* [\[A Gentle World through the Perspective of Children with Developmental Disabilities\] Episode 3: Takuya-kun Having Trouble with Friendships―The World Surrounding Children with ASD](https://www.childresearch.net/projects/special/2023_14.html)
* [\[South Korea\] Current Situation and Issues of Inclusive Education for Preschool Children in South Korea - II](https://www.childresearch.net/projects/ecec/2023_09.html)
* [\[Video\] Thoughts on Inclusive Education (3)](https://www.childresearch.net/projects/special/2023_13.html)
* [\[Video\] Thoughts on Inclusive Education (2)](https://www.childresearch.net/projects/special/2023_12.html)
* [Promoting Children's Resilience for Nurturing Competent Citizens for the Future](https://www.childresearch.net/projects/fullpaper/2023_01.html)
* [\[Perspectives of Traditional Culture of the Matrilineal Mosuo of Lugu Lake\] Part 6: Mosuo Women's Choice of Marriage in Different Times](https://www.childresearch.net/papers/new/2023_03.html)

(c) 1996-2024, Child Research Net

Child Research Net is supported by BERD (Benesse Educational Research and Development Institute). [](http://www.benesse.co.jp/)

* Main Research Topics
* Other Research Topics
